<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recon Technology Consulting</title>
    <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://recon.com.tr/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Recon Technology Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://recon.com.tr/media/logo_hu15455760525912019561.png</url>
      <title>Recon Technology Consulting</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial fraud detection tool</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/wallet_fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/wallet_fraud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;fraud-detection-for-digital-wallets&#34;&gt;Fraud detection for digital wallets&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are developing a rule-based product that complies with MASAK (Financial Crimes Investigation Board) criteria to protect customer balances in digital wallets. Approaches emerging from discussions with various licensed electronic money institutions and our project work at Dijitalpark Technopark are reflected in the product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As our product is our own design and software, it is open to customization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-it-ready-for-immediate-use&#34;&gt;Is it ready for immediate use?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can contact us to test our Digital Wallet Fraud Detection product at an early stage and to use it when it&amp;rsquo;s finalized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-there-ai-support&#34;&gt;Is there AI support?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is currently no machine learning or artificial intelligence support. However, these features are planned to be added in the upcoming period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;usage-and-features&#34;&gt;Usage and features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages to be sent to the fraud detection system during transactions are evaluated and responded to in real-time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scenario management is provided through a web interface with unique methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions to be taken for detected transactions can be defined.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transactions are placed in a separate pool and evaluated by operators via the web by creating case files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transaction control flow and scenarios are open to dynamic updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The fraud database is kept fully encrypted (encryption at rest). Compliance with regulations and privacy requirements can be ensured.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The web interface can provide authorization management, login with Active Directory (LDAP), and a maker-checker control structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;compatibility&#34;&gt;Compatibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is suitable for container platforms. It can be operated in compliance with TCMB (Central Bank of Turkey), MASAK, and BDDK (Banking Regulation and Supervision Agency) regulations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTRANS reporting automation</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/btrans_reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/btrans_reporting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;challenges-of-btrans-reporting&#34;&gt;Challenges of BTRANS reporting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The requirement to submit BTRANS reports daily has created a need for automating the reporting process. The routine for manually retrieving reports from the database or report services, uploading them to institutional servers, and verifying them is clearly defined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the BTRANS automation solution, the reports for the previous day will be prepared by the morning. According to the data control standards of the Turkish Revenue Administration (GİB), checks are performed to prevent the submission of incorrect data. If errors are found in the generated data, they can be identified before the files are sent to GİB, allowing for corrections at the source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reports can be previewed via a web interface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Files are generated in Parquet format and automatically sent to SFTP servers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This service is designed exclusively for organizations obligated to send data to BTRANS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-it-ready-to-use&#34;&gt;Is it ready to use?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, it is ready to use. Installations are carried out on your company’s servers for deployment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-there-a-web-interface&#34;&gt;Is there a web interface?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, there is a web interface. It features authority management, maker-checker workflow, and user login with Active Directory (LDAP). All user actions are logged for auditing purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get in touch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simplify your BTRANS reporting processes with RECON today. For more information, reach out to us using one of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://recon.com.tr/contact&#34;&gt;contact options&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital wallet integration solutions</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/wallet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At RECON, we know that digital wallets will increasingly become a part of our lives. To this end, we offer the following services to organizations that want to integrate with digital wallet ecosystem APIs and modernize their services:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank integrations, account transactions and transfers, card transactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turkish ID / KPS / NVI integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KYC / KYB / AML / Address verification (domestic and international)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IBAN validation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BKM BIN query&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration with national and international money transfer organizations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We primarily serve licensed institutions in the finance sector and are looking to work with new ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, we can provide necessary services to companies that want to integrate into the fintech ecosystem, have developed a comprehensive and customized roadmap with banks and fintechs, and wish to make their own detailed component choices.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast, simple, reliable regulatory reporting</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/legal_reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/legal_reporting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-recon&#34;&gt;Why RECON?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the financial technology sector, regulatory reporting is becoming more complex every day. We, at RECON, are here to simplify this process for you. As a team specialized in regulatory reporting, we use our technology and expertise to offer you fast, reliable, and fully compliant reporting services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-features&#34;&gt;Our features:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast Reporting: Your time is valuable. That&amp;rsquo;s why we accelerate your regulatory reporting processes, allowing you to dedicate more time to your business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full Compliance: Our reports, prepared with the latest regulations and standards in mind, ensure full compliance with legal requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Security: Ensuring the security of our clients&amp;rsquo; data is our top priority. We protect your data using the most up-to-date security protocols.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User-Friendly Interface: We simplify the reporting process with an intuitive and easy-to-use interface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-we-work&#34;&gt;How we work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Step - Needs Analysis: We conduct a detailed interview with you to understand your business&amp;rsquo;s specific needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reporting Process: Using the latest technologies, we provide a solution that will process your data quickly and effectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final Check and Delivery: Your reports are prepared in accordance with legal standards and submitted for your approval. If desired, they can be automatically sent to relevant authorities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get in touch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start simplifying your regulatory reporting processes with RECON today. For more information, &lt;a href=&#34;https://recon.com.tr/contact&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; through one of our communication options.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our privacy principles consist of both &lt;a href=&#34;#gizlilik-privacy&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;#cerez-cookie&#34;&gt;Cookie Policy&lt;/a&gt; texts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gizlilik-privacy&#34;&gt;PRIVACY AND PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION POLICY&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At recon.com.tr, we prioritize the security of your personal data. Your personal data is processed and stored in compliance with Law No. 6698 on the Protection of Personal Data (&amp;ldquo;KVKK&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-how-your-personal-data-may-be-processed&#34;&gt;1. How Your Personal Data May Be Processed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In accordance with the KVKK No. 6698, your personal data shared with recon.com.tr can be processed by us in whole or in part, automatically or through non-automated methods, provided that it is part of any data recording system, by obtaining, recording, storing, modifying, reorganizing, in short, by subjecting it to any kind of processing on data. Any operation performed on data within the scope of KVKK is considered as “processing of personal data.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-purposes-and-legal-grounds-for-processing-your-personal-data&#34;&gt;2. Purposes and Legal Grounds for Processing Your Personal Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The personal data you share will be processed for the following purposes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To fulfill the requirements of the services we provide to our customers, in compliance with the contractual and technological needs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide information to public authorities, courts, and relevant officials, when requested and required by legislation, in matters related to public security and legal disputes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To offer a wide range of opportunities to our members or share these opportunities with individuals or institutions capable of offering them within the legal framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To analyze advertising preferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data will be processed in accordance with KVKK No. 6698 and the relevant secondary regulations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-information-regarding-the-transfer-of-your-personal-data-to-third-parties-or-institutions&#34;&gt;3. Information Regarding the Transfer of Your Personal Data to Third Parties or Institutions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the purposes mentioned above, the personal data you share with recon.com.tr may be transferred to the following individuals/institutions: our main shareholders, shareholders, advertisers, direct or indirect domestic/foreign affiliates; companies using recon.com.tr&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure, and other related persons and organizations. In addition, your personal data may be shared with third-party companies, organizations, or individuals we collaborate with, either domestically or abroad, for services we provide or receive under the title of Data Processor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regulations regarding cookies used for advertising purposes are outlined in the recon.com.tr &lt;a href=&#34;#cerez-cookie&#34;&gt;Cookie Policy&lt;/a&gt;, which forms part of the “Privacy and Personal Data Protection Policy” that you are currently reading. For more information on our Cookie Policy, please click &lt;a href=&#34;#cerez-cookie&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-how-your-personal-data-is-collected&#34;&gt;4. How Your Personal Data is Collected&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data can be collected through:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forms on the recon.com.tr website and mobile applications, including details such as name, surname, address, phone number, business or private email address, and user preferences made during login to pages with a username and password. Data on the performed transactions&amp;rsquo; IP records, cookie data collected by the browser, browsing time and details, and location data;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individuals sharing personal data with recon.com.tr for commercial purposes, job applications, or offers via business cards, CVs, or other means, either in physical or virtual environments, face-to-face, remotely, verbally, in writing, or electronically;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additionally, data obtained indirectly from other channels such as websites, blogs, competitions, surveys, campaigns, or similar (micro) websites and social media platforms (Facebook, Twitter, Google, Instagram, Snapchat, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;5-personal-data-obtained-before-the-implementation-of-kvkk&#34;&gt;5. Personal Data Obtained Before the Implementation of KVKK&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As recon.com.tr started its operations after the effective date of KVKK (April 7, 2016), no personal data was stored prior to this date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;6-transfer-of-personal-data&#34;&gt;6. Transfer of Personal Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data collected through any of the methods mentioned above, processed in Turkey or transferred abroad for storage, may be transferred to service providers (accredited by the Personal Data Board and providing adequate protection for personal data), provided it remains within the scope of the KVKK and is in compliance with the purposes of the contract.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data may be transferred to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our business partners with whom we collaborate or receive services to promote and provide our products and services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Authorized authorities responsible for determining your location in case of emergency calls;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regulatory and supervisory bodies, courts, enforcement offices, and other official institutions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legal entities with whom recon.com.tr has a commercial relationship and who possess your phone number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;7-retention-and-protection-of-personal-data&#34;&gt;7. Retention and Protection of Personal Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recon.com.tr is responsible for protecting the systems and databases where your personal data is stored, preventing unauthorized access, and ensuring data security as required by Article 12 of the KVKK. In the event that personal data is obtained by others through unlawful means, recon.com.tr will immediately inform the Personal Data Protection Board in writing and take appropriate legal actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;8-keeping-personal-data-up-to-date&#34;&gt;8. Keeping Personal Data Up to Date&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In accordance with Article 4 of the KVKK, recon.com.tr is obliged to keep your personal data accurate and up to date. Members are required to share or update their correct and current data through the website or mobile application to ensure recon.com.tr can fulfill its legal obligations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;9-rights-of-personal-data-owners-under-kvkk&#34;&gt;9. Rights of Personal Data Owners Under KVKK&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of October 7, 2016, in accordance with Article 11 of the KVKK, Personal Data Owners have the following rights:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To learn whether their personal data has been processed,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To request information if their personal data has been processed,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To learn the purpose of processing their personal data and whether it is being used in line with the intended purpose,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To know third parties to whom personal data is transferred domestically or abroad,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To request the correction of incomplete or inaccurate personal data,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To request the deletion or destruction of personal data under the conditions set out in Article 7 of the KVKK,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To request notification of any correction, deletion, or destruction of personal data to third parties to whom it has been transferred,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To object to any unfavorable results arising from exclusively automated systems analyzing their data,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To request compensation for damages incurred due to the unlawful processing of personal data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;10-contact-and-application-methods&#34;&gt;10. Contact and Application Methods&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Data Controller Representative to be appointed by recon.com.tr will be announced in the Data Controllers Registry when the legal infrastructure is provided and published at this address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal Data Owners can direct their questions, opinions, or requests to the email address &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@recon.com.tr&#34;&gt;info@recon.com.tr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recon.com.tr will respond to inquiries, either positively or negatively, within 30 days of receiving the request, providing a reasoned response in writing or electronically. The main principle is that the necessary actions for requests are free of charge. However, if the processing of requests incurs a cost, recon.com.tr reserves the right to charge a fee. These fees will be determined based on the tariff set by the Personal Data Protection Board under Article 13 of the Law on the Protection of Personal Data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By sharing your personal data on our website, applications, and other channels, you acknowledge that you have given explicit consent based on informed and voluntary consent defined as having a specific focus under KVKK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This policy was last updated on 01/12/2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cerez-cookie&#34;&gt;COOKIE POLICY&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Cookie Policy is part of our &lt;a href=&#34;#gizlilik-privacy&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-cookies&#34;&gt;What Are Cookies?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cookies are small data files placed on your computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other devices through your browser by the website you visit. Cookies allow the website to recognize the user’s device, store certain information (e.g., user preferences), and enhance the user’s experience. Cookies generally do not contain personal data unless it is directly identifiable to the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-are-cookies-used&#34;&gt;Why Are Cookies Used?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recon.com.tr uses cookies for the following purposes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enhance the website’s performance and make its use more efficient,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To analyze visitor trends and behavior on the website, enabling us to improve the user experience,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To store user preferences and settings (e.g., remembering your language preference or login information for future visits),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To improve the security of the website and protect user data,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To display relevant advertisements or content to users based on their interests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;types-of-cookies-used&#34;&gt;Types of Cookies Used&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recon.com.tr may use different types of cookies:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;: These cookies are temporary and are deleted when the user closes the browser. They help keep the website running smoothly during the visit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;: Help improve website performance by collecting data about user interaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Functional Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;: Remember user preferences and settings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advertising and Third-Party Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;: These cookies are placed by third-party services used by the website (e.g., social media platforms or advertisers). These cookies allow third parties to collect data about users and track their behavior across multiple websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cookie-usage-purposes&#34;&gt;Cookie Usage Purposes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purposes of using cookies by recon.com.tr are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For security purposes: recon.com.tr may use cookies to enable functionalities on this site or detect irregular behavior, ensuring the administration and security of its systems.
For functionality purposes: recon.com.tr may use cookies to facilitate the use of its systems and provide user-specific features, such as remembering users&amp;rsquo; information and past choices.
For performance purposes: recon.com.tr may use cookies to assess and analyze user behavior and interactions with sent messages to improve and measure the performance of its systems.
For advertising purposes: recon.com.tr may use cookies to deliver advertisements and similar content based on users&amp;rsquo; interests, either through its own or third-party systems. These cookies may also measure the effectiveness of advertisements or analyze click behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-of-cookies-for-advertising-purposes&#34;&gt;Use of Cookies for Advertising Purposes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recon.com.tr uses the Google AdSense advertising system. This system includes the DoubleClick DART cookie used in ads displayed on publisher websites through Google’s AdSense for Content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a third-party vendor, Google uses cookies to serve ads on our site. These cookies allow Google to serve ads to users based on their visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. You can opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (excluding your name, address, email address, or phone number) from your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about products and services of interest to you. To learn more about this practice, your options to prevent the use of such information by these companies, and to find more details, you can consult the NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers (PDF), Appendix A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;controlling-and-deleting-cookies&#34;&gt;Controlling and Deleting Cookies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can change your preferences regarding the use of cookies, or block or delete them by changing your browser settings. Many browsers offer options to control cookies, such as accepting or rejecting them, accepting only certain types of cookies, or notifying you when a website wants to store cookies on your device. It is also possible to delete cookies that have been previously saved in your browser. Cookie control or deletion processes may vary depending on the browser you are using. You can find instructions on how to allow, block, or delete cookies for some popular browsers via the links below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The method to change cookie usage preferences depends on your browser type and can be learned from the relevant service provider at any time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This policy was last updated on 12/01/2024.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We simplify legal reporting processes</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/news/btrans-raporlama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/news/btrans-raporlama/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Türkiye, TCMB-licensed payment services and electronic money institutions are required to regularly produce various reports. Given the operational workload of payment services and the regulatory intensity of the legislation, the already limited profitability imposes a heavy additional burden and responsibilities on companies in the face of high costs and difficulties to fulfill new reporting requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reporting&#34;&gt;Reporting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The content of reports generated by TCMB-licensed institutions is generally similar. The primary difference lies in the data compilation phase. Once data is compiled and verified, the legal authorities define the nature of the reporting content, making it natural for reports to be similar. In the current ecosystem, as each institution has its own software platform, and legal reporting requirements often emerge later, institutions must design the operational and technical infrastructure necessary to prepare their reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, this is not the main area of expertise for many companies, and it can become an overly complex process for firms that do not write the software themselves, leading to issues such as failure to meet legal demands on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;value-proposition&#34;&gt;Value Proposition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Recon Technology, we saw a potential commercial value in this area and developed a low-cost, high-value legal reporting product for companies. Our product is currently used for the BTRANS notifications required by the Revenue Administration. It meets technical and legal requirements, offers flexible integration alternatives with your data, and can be deployed on-premise or on cloud infrastructure compliant with financial regulations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to its modular structure, it can be added as an additional legal reporting module without affecting your existing workflows and integrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quality&#34;&gt;Quality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our product&amp;rsquo;s controls and software testing phases are carried out comprehensively, allowing for smooth operation from the very beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With our team&amp;rsquo;s banking and fintech experience, accurate processing of high volumes of financial data, design of services capable of operating under load, and preventative engineering approaches toward potential issues provide a significant advantage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We aim to contribute to the financial ecosystem and help payment services and electronic money institutions focus on their core business. You can use the BTRANS reporting module with confidence and at the best possible cost. For more information, please &lt;a href=&#34;https://recon.com.tr/en/contact/&#34; title=&#34;Contact&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products and Services</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services_select/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services_select/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
