<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fraud | Recon Technology Consulting</title>
    <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/tag/fraud/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://recon.com.tr/en/tag/fraud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Fraud</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://recon.com.tr/media/logo_hu15455760525912019561.png</url>
      <title>Fraud</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/tag/fraud/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial fraud detection tool</title>
      <link>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/wallet_fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recon.com.tr/en/products_services/wallet_fraud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;fraud-detection-for-digital-wallets&#34;&gt;Fraud detection for digital wallets&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are developing a rule-based product that complies with MASAK (Financial Crimes Investigation Board) criteria to protect customer balances in digital wallets. Approaches emerging from discussions with various licensed electronic money institutions and our project work at Dijitalpark Technopark are reflected in the product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As our product is our own design and software, it is open to customization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-it-ready-for-immediate-use&#34;&gt;Is it ready for immediate use?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can contact us to test our Digital Wallet Fraud Detection product at an early stage and to use it when it&amp;rsquo;s finalized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-there-ai-support&#34;&gt;Is there AI support?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is currently no machine learning or artificial intelligence support. However, these features are planned to be added in the upcoming period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;usage-and-features&#34;&gt;Usage and features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages to be sent to the fraud detection system during transactions are evaluated and responded to in real-time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scenario management is provided through a web interface with unique methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions to be taken for detected transactions can be defined.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transactions are placed in a separate pool and evaluated by operators via the web by creating case files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transaction control flow and scenarios are open to dynamic updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The fraud database is kept fully encrypted (encryption at rest). Compliance with regulations and privacy requirements can be ensured.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The web interface can provide authorization management, login with Active Directory (LDAP), and a maker-checker control structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;compatibility&#34;&gt;Compatibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is suitable for container platforms. It can be operated in compliance with TCMB (Central Bank of Turkey), MASAK, and BDDK (Banking Regulation and Supervision Agency) regulations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
